# **Emil Ismayilzada**

- +36301567713
- ismailzadeh.emil@gmail.com
- iamemil.github.io
- Debrecen, Hungary

#### SUMMARY

Highly motivated and creative software developer with more than 2 years of experience in building web, desktop apps, RESTful APIs. Skilled in C#, ASP.NET, ReactJS development and Database design. Created platforms such as award winning homework management system, event attendee management platform, expense tracking platform based on crowdsourcing to help users manage their expenses

#### EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern 04/2021 - Present

VisitMe

• Working on the development of various Web (ReactJS, ASP.NET, C#) apps for customers such as guest list app for events, easy-to-use menu page for customers

**ASP.NET Developer** 05/2021 - 06/2021

Abdel's Kitchen

- · Created online exclusive meal order system / POS with ASP.NET, HTML/CSS/JS stack
- Customers can create their profile through registration
- · After approval of admin, it is possible to use all features of website
- Owner can manage orders, customers, items which are being sold, and view statistics about sales

Front End Developer Intern 03/2021 - 05/2021

LimeLight Renhold

- Created responsive web pages based on tasks
- · Improved existing web components to match customer needs

**ASP.NET Developer** 06/2020 - 07/2020

CavApp

- · Created QA forum with payment feature.
- Users can ask questions by payment, and they can choose an answer out of the answers coming from other users.
- · Chosen answer user gets paid
- · Users can use their balance in website or withdraw

Web Developer 02/2018 - 05/2018

Taskie

- · Created school system for homework
- · Teachers can assign tasks to classes and students can view them
- Drops the chance of forgetting homework to a minimum level, as everything is saved online and accessible with a student account
- Project won 1st place in GoldenByte IT championship in Baku, Azerbaijan and 2nd place in GoldenByte International IT championship in Kyiv, Ukraine

### EDUCATION

## **Computer Science**

University of Debrecen - Master's Degree

Computer Science 2022

University of Debrecen - Bachelor's Degree

GPA 4.42/5.0

SKILLS

C# ASP.NET

Java SQL

PL/SQL HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Git Flutter

Native

React

LANGUAGES

Azerbaijani

Turkish

Fluent

English Fluent